chetanasforum.com 2013-06-20

# ChetanaS - Privacy Policy... - Rules & Regulations - ChetanaSforum

###  [ #1  ](http://www.chetanasforum.com/index.php?showtopic=18709#entry34139 "ChetanaS - Privacy Policy...: post #1")

Posted 03 March 2008 - 06:33 PM

**ChetanaS - Privacy Policy**

At ChetanaS, we highly respect your privacy. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. We outline the types of information collected by us when you use the services of ChetanaS and the steps taken by us to safeguard the information collected from you. We believe it helps you to take the necessary decision of whether to share your information with us or not.

By using the products, services and websites of ChetanaS (collectively known as ChetanaS's "services"), you agree to be abide by our Privacy Policy mentioned below.

 **The Information We Collect From You**

For every visit to ChetanaS websites, we record visitor's details like IP Address, Location, OS, Browser Type, Visit Length and other computer specific information. This type of information is used to learn about user preferences and to make our services more useful and friendly.

When you register for our services, we collect personal information like Name, Email Id, Email Preferences...etc. However most of the personal details are optional.

However we DO NOT sell, rent or share any details entered by you or email address through which you might have contacted us or entered during the registration process in our ChetanaS network.

You will receive our email alerts (about new content updates in the website and the important happenings) ONLY IF you opted for during registration or at a later point of time. Unsubscription instructions are clearly included in every email sent by us and you can unsubscribe or change your email preferences at any time. 

**Cookie Management and Web beacons**

We (Or our Advertisers) may access and set cookies using Web beacons, also known as single-pixel GIFs, which are invisible graphical images. These Web beacons tell us useful information regarding our site such as which pages users access. However we DO NOT sell, rent or share any of these detailed obtained by us.

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

 **DoubleClick DART Cookie**

\- Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our website.  
\- Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.  
\- Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google Ad and Content Network Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html "External link").   
\- You can [Check Here](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx "External link") to know more details about DoubleClick DART Cookie.

 **Third Party Advertisements**

To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with few third-party companies that we allow to place ads in our web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, third-party ad serving companies (such as Google's AdSense) may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. It could also access and set cookies in your browser, use web beacons as mentioned above. For further information, please consult the Privacy Policy of respective ad serving companies. (For example, [Privacy Policy of Google (Adsense)](http://www.google.com/privacy.html "External link"))

 **Contact us for more info**

If you have any privacy related issues, you may contact the administrator of this website and get your issues resolved or you may unsubscribe from ChetanaS services at any time.

 **Privacy Policy - subject to change**

If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes at our Web site to notify you of these changes. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically or directly [Contact Us](http://www.chetanasforum.com/index.php?&autocom=contactform) for any clarifications. 

**VERY IMPORTANT MESSAGE FROM CHETANA ****

[ **CLICK HERE TO REGISTER**](http://www.chetanasforum.com/index.php?act=Reg&CODE=00) in this forum to get the best **Career Guidance & Latest Job Updates** directly into your mailbox. Registration is simple & hardly takes 1 minute. **5,00,000** people are already part of this **ChetanaS** job revolution.

\-------------------------------------------------------------------------  
Best Wishes...ChetanaS  
\-------------------------------------------------------------------------

\- LIKE our FaceBook Page to get job updates

\- JAVA / J2EE Jobs, Walk-In & FAQ

\- TESTING Jobs, Walk-In & FAQ

\- 6000 Latest Placement Papers

\- Jobs & Career Guidance

\- Latest Jobs for Freshers & Experienced  
\------------------------------------------------------------------------- 
  *[03 March 2008 - 06:33 PM]: 2008-03-03T13:03:45+00:00
